http://www.nypirg.org/policies/privacy

Privacy Policy
Content Information we collect How we use the information we collect How we protect your information External links
Your consent
Changes to our privacy policy Contacting us
This privacy statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for nypirg.org. This website was created and is managed by the New York Public Interest Research Group Fund (NYPIRG).
Your identity and contact information will be treated confidentially and will not be shared.
Information we collect
We collect information from you when you sign up for email updates and alerts, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
How we use the information we collect
Any of the information that we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
• To send periodic emails: The email address that you provide, if you sign up for email updates and alerts, will only be used
to send you information and updates.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
• To improve our website: We continually strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback that we receive from you.
How we protect your information
NYPIRG will not sell or give away any personal information that you provide (such as your name or contact information), nor will it make available your information to any outside organization without your express consent.
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and who are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
External links
Some links on the nypirg.org website point to sites which are located outside of the nypirg.org domain and, therefore, are not managed or controlled by NYPIRG. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our privacy policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us by mail at the address below or by email at nypirg@nypirg.org.
